[{"answer": "Good, Piers.", "docId": "130517pmt", "aSentId": 13, "question": "Bob, how are you?", "qSentId": 12}, {"answer": "I couldn't think of a better person, really, given the events of the last month, in a sense.", "docId": "130517pmt", "aSentId": 15, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 14}, {"answer": "Well, in the case of the gun situation, the only reason I addressed it was because the jumping off point was a murder-suicide involving an NFL player.", "docId": "130517pmt", "aSentId": 26, "question": "What do you say to those people?", "qSentId": 25}, {"answer": "Some of it was, yes.", "docId": "130517pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "Yes, but see, I thought the reaction was absurd and, you know?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "Well, you see, Bob, the NRA is not the problem, as you and I know, because I've got a clip here from Wayne LaPierre.", "docId": "130517pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "Why do they stand in front of reasonable reforms?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "But -- but let me ask a different question.", "docId": "130517pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "And that's what happened with a 5 -year- old kid -- I'm sorry that they had to suffer a tragedy -- but what sort of parent buys a kid a usable -- not a toy gun, but a usable gun with ammunition and then walks away and the kid kills his 2 -year-old sister?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "And let's also understand, the NRA is a gun lobby, like any other lobbying organization --", "docId": "130517pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "Yes, you can blame irresponsible parents, but what kind of society that is part of the great superpower of the world allows a company like Crickett to be deliberately marketing and selling guns to 5-year-olds?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "Well, look, the NRA convention just concluded in Houston.", "docId": "130517pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "Where is the outrage?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "I think that puts it mildly.", "docId": "130517pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "Care to respond, Bob?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "Yes, sir.", "docId": "130517pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "Gerald?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "Well, I wanted to be a sports announcer because I -- I loved sports as a kid and I was also enchanted by the voices of sport.", "docId": "130517pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "What made you desire to become a sports broadcaster in the first place, and since becoming one of the best, what is your take on how the profession has changed since your early days at NBC in the 1970s?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "Well, I think the evidence was accumulating year after year and there was so much smoke, you figure there had to be fire.", "docId": "130517pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "But what was the moment for you when the blinkers maybe came off and you realized he is a cheat?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "He was a very good liar, because he was intelligent and he had a series of facts, or what he purported to be facts, rather than evasions, and he did have the one thing going for him, that he had been tested repeatedly in and out of competition and never failed a drug test.", "docId": "130517pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "And he was a good liar, wasn't he?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130517pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "He was bigger, though, wasn't he?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "You know, I didn't take it personally.", "docId": "130517pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "He looked you, Bob Costas, in the eye, one of the most respected men, yourself, in American sport, and just sold you a complete pack of lies?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130517pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "ORGAN: Did he ever apologize to you?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "(INAUDIBLE) is hot.", "docId": "130517pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "Roll that tape, will you?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130517pmt", "aSentId": 344, "question": "Would you let me finish?", "qSentId": 343}, {"answer": "Well, here was the deal.", "docId": "130517pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "Bob, what were you thinking when that was all going on?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "Well, a couple of things about this.", "docId": "130517pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "It's like some anachronistic old gentleman's club, isn't it?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "This is an unbelievable interview.", "docId": "130517pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "Daniel?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "I can't narrow it to one.", "docId": "130517pmt", "aSentId": 462, "question": "What is the single best sports moment you have ever seen?", "qSentId": 461}, {"answer": "Perhaps the greatest all around athlete would be Jim Brown, the great American football player, who also could have been the greatest lacrosse player who ever lived, undoubtedly could have played basketball in the NBA.", "docId": "130517pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "Who is the greatest sportsman you have ever seen in any sport, for whatever reason?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "I think a lot of people are able to separate.", "docId": "130517pmt", "aSentId": 492, "question": "It is about winning, isn't it?", "qSentId": 491}, {"answer": "Well, there's some validity in that.", "docId": "130517pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "There are the cheats and the non-cheats, aren't there?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "Well, I interviewed Ted Williams, who some people think is the greatest hitter of all time, in 1988, at a time when he had not done an interview, radio or television, at all, in 15, 16 years.", "docId": "130517pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "What would you say?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "130517pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "In retrospect, was that true?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "Or the daddy.", "docId": "130517pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "Because you hadn't been the ball player you felt you should have been?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "Well, I could say that, you know, I have done some of those things.", "docId": "130517pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "Completely innocent and falsely accused in every aspect?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "I could ask the same question of you.", "docId": "130517pmt", "aSentId": 587, "question": "Is there one?", "qSentId": 586}, {"answer": "I'm in a very, very good place.", "docId": "130517pmt", "aSentId": 606, "question": "Do you believe you finally got to the right place for you?", "qSentId": 605}, {"answer": "You know, Dick Clark went to Syracuse as I did.", "docId": "130517pmt", "aSentId": 618, "question": "And will you share it?", "qSentId": 617}, {"answer": "Let's go to a quick quiz.", "docId": "130517pmt", "aSentId": 658, "question": "So why change it?", "qSentId": 657}, {"answer": "I would say the police probably brought you home in the middle of the night.", "docId": "130517pmt", "aSentId": 662, "question": "Do you know what a -- if I said I was bowling you a googly, and I had two silly mid ones and a fine leg, would you know what the hell I'm talking about?", "qSentId": 661}, {"answer": "I'm sure it doesn't involve him.", "docId": "130517pmt", "aSentId": 684, "question": "Do you?", "qSentId": 683}, {"answer": "That's an McRib.", "docId": "130517pmt", "aSentId": 691, "question": "Do you get that with fries at McDonald's?", "qSentId": 690}]